WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
What's the matter?
After pursuing me like that,
what's up with you?
You're not even able to touch me...
What a laugh!
Sakura-chan...
I don't know how far I can go, but...
I have to give it... my best shot!
Explosion!
These are the
Naruto Ninja Chronicles!!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Here goes!
From this moment on,
Secret Ultimate Taijutsu technique!
Uzumaki Naruto...
Clone Body Slam!
— Now!
Okay!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Once again...
Take this!
Leaf Village Secret Ultimate
Taijutsu technique
learned from Kakashi-sensei!
A Thousand Years of Death!
An enema?
Boom.
Sasuke...?
That was a splendid blow.
D-Did that get him?
Gaara...
Doing all that work...
And managing just one blow, huh?
S-Shut up!
He attacked the base of the tail
which has the weakest defense...
Even though I'm not wounded,
I can't absorb the impact.
Did I underestimate him too much?
Hey, Naruto...
Sakura... Go rescue her
if it's the last thing you do!
And after you've rescued her...
take Sakura and
lose no time in fleeing.
You, if anyone, can do it!
Sasuke... You...
I still have the ability...
to hold him in check for a while.
If things end here...
it would just mean that
was the extent of the man I am.
I lost everything once...
I don't want to see...
any precious comrades die
right before my eyes again.
Precious... comrades...
I will not allow my comrades...
to be killed, no matter what.
I see...
That's right.
Because he resembles me...
Because he has gone through life
with the same loneliness
and sadness as I have...
That guy who continued to fight
in solitude for himself,
I thought... he was strong.
Naruto...
But that's not the meaning
of true strength...
If one fights just for
oneself in solitude...
one can't really become strong...
Is there someone who
is precious to you?
When a person wants to protect
someone who is precious to him...
it's then that they truly...
become... strong.
You will... become strong.
He's releasing such
massive amount of Chakra!
That's... Naruto?!
No matter what, I will...
protect you!
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
He's pretty good, this one.
I've kept you waiting
a long time!
The spiraling series of Uzumaki Naruto's
Ninja Handbook starts now!
W-What's up with this...
large number of clones?!
What the hell is this?
T-This is... amazing!
You are pretty promising.
You... This is...
Sasuke, you get yourself
a good rest.
Leave the rest to Uzumaki Naruto!
This guy is...
All right! Everyone! Here I go!
that Naruto?!
Jump!
Naruto's... Ninja... Handbook!
Everywhere...
Shuriken!
My body hasn't fully recovered...
My only choice is to
use Sand as a defense!
— U! Zu! Ma! Ki! 2K Naruto...!
— Barrage!
T-This guy...!
— This time, I'll use both legs...
— and go for a 4K Barrage!
Who the hell is that...?
Suddenly...
Unbelievable...
To get Gaara in that state...
Where does that strength come from?
No way!
There's no way...
No way I'll... lose to... a guy like this...!
W-What's... that?
It finally... emerged.
The Perfect Possession!
This is...
the monster inside that guy.
I didn't think you would
expose this form!
Naruto!
Damn... my body...!
My Chakra has...
with all those clones earlier on...
Sakura-chan!
D-Damn...!
I, Inu, Tori, Saru, Hitsuji...
This will mark your end...
— Sand Burial!
— Summoning Jutsu!
It's amazing that he can utilize
a Summoning Jutsu in that state...
I will protect...
Sakura-chan!
Uzumaki Naruto...
You continue to give me
such pleasure...
Naruto...
What in the... world...?
My hours of practice
are finally paying off!
I can do it!
— What is this?
— Huh?
Not you again!
What in the world do you want?
Huh?!
That must be...
the Shukaku of the Sand.
Chief Toad!
Come join me in this fight!
No way!
What?!
Why would I go out of my way
and fight a guy like that?
That's idiotic!
Why?!
You told me the other day that you
would make me your henchman!
It's only natural for a chief
to help out his henchman!
That's respect and duty, right?!
It's true I told you
I'd make you my henchman...
But we haven't even exchanged
cups of sake to seal our relationship yet...
Gimme a break! I'm still underage!
I can't drink alcohol!
Don't say that and just listen
to what this guy says, Pop!
Huh?! Pop?!
Why are you here, Gamakichi?
I had lots of time on my hands,
so I came to visit...
Huh? Huh?
You're father and son?
Then that guy over there
tried to bully me!
What was that?!
When that happened,
this guy here rescued me...
He clashed with that monster...
Pretty interesting guy.
I see...
Kid... I recognize you
as my henchman...
and I'll show you what duty
and respect means!
I'll make you pay the price
good and proper, you underling!
Hang on tight!
How's that?!
Awesome...
What a guy...
He's so heavy,
I could barely manage to
thrust my dagger through him.
If I don't hurry up,
this battle will change
the shape of the landscape.
Hey! Hey! Chief!
Sakura-chan is over that way,
so don't move that way!
Please lure him in this direction.
Sakura-chan...?
That's his girlfriend, Pop.
I've got to take that guy down.
Otherwise, I won't be able
to rescue Sakura-chan!
Interesting!
This is interesting!
Uzumaki Naruto!
T-This isn't good!
That Gaara...
He's intending to do that thing.
I better get out of here!
Huh...? That is...
That's... the medium...?
To thank you for entertaining me
up to now...
I'll show you the real power...
of the Sand Spirit!
The circles under his eyes...
Those are symptoms of
insomnia which indicate
that the medium is also possessed
by the Shukaku of the Sand.
Insomnia...?
Those who are possessed
by the Demon Raccoon Shukaku
are unable to sleep soundly
through the entire night.
Because of the terror...
If one sleeps, Shukaku will slowly
eat away at their personality
and eventually that person
is no longer himself.
Because he normally
doesn't get much sleep...
the medium's personality
tends to... become unstable.
Oh...
Therefore, usually while
the medium is awake,
the power of Shukaku is
normally controlled.
However...
when that medium sleeps...
Playing Possum Jutsu!
He's done it...!
W-What's gonna happen, Chief?
If one sets Playing Possum Jutsu
into motion...
...the Shukaku will appear!
I'm finally able to emerge!
That's the Shukaku?
He's pretty funky...
Right away!
The guy I wanna kill! You!
I'm gonna jump...
Huh?
Wind Style: Air Bullets!
Water Style: Water Bullets!
That's practically a storm...
What kind of a battle is this...?!
Chief! I told you,
not in that direction!
Shut up! I know!
Air Bullets!
Water Bullets!
Too bad...
This isn't good, Chief!
There's one shot left...!
Yeah! I killed it...
I killed it!
That hurts...!
How dare you shoot me
with bullets containing
stupid amounts of Chakra!
Even I can't take that many shots!
What should we do?!
For a start,
wake up that medium kid!
It will release that Jutsu!
How do we go about waking him?!
Give him a good punch!
Water Bullets!
Like I'll take that!
Now!
Chief, I can't hit him
unless you hold him down!
This Toad doesn't have fangs or claws
to hold that guy's movement.
What should we do then?!
We'll use the Transform Jutsu to
change into something that has those!
But with that said...
I'm not particularly good
at transformations.
Huh?
So you will act as my will
and make the Sign!
What?!
Time for a combined transformation!
Uh... Okay!
We got to have fangs and claws!
Umm...
Let's go!
Wait...
Hey, w-wait a second...!
F-Fangs and claws... Fangs and claws...
Fangs and claws!
Transform!
Transform Jutsu!
That's the...!
gaman no renzoku dattaro
a cycle of hardship, right?
kokoro de naiteita ndarou
inside, we were crying, right?
jibun de kimeta sono yume dake wa yuzurenai ndarou
but the one thing we won't give up is the dream we've chosen, right?
wakiyaku dakedo
it's a secondary role
kage no hito dakedo
a role in the shadows
yume to mukiau toki kurai
but in reaching for that dream
man naka ni isasete shoujiki ni isasete
let us stay centered, let us stay true
ima made nandomo nan toka akiramezu ni
over and over, we hung on without giving up
ima made nandomo tachi agatte kita janai ka
over and over, we kept coming back up
ima made nandomo
over and over, we believed and dreamed
bokura
nandomo
shinjite
yume mite nandomo
ima made nandomo baka o mite kita janai ka
over and over, we've seen fools
ima made nandomo hito no kage ni tatte kita janai ka
over and over, we've stood in the shadows of others
saa shuyaku da yo jibun no yume kurai wagamama de isasete
now, it's our turn... let us bask in our dreams
I don't know about your past,
and my past doesn't matter either!
I only have people who I must protect.
Hey you with no eyebrows!
Let's just end this as similar fighters.
I will finish this with my next hit.
This will be, absolutely and totally,
the last one!
Next time:
"Break the Limit! Light and Darkness."